memberspring.com 2011-08-14

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

High Card Marketing, LLC., the parent company of MemberSpring, is committed to customer service and strives to provide a private and secure browsing experience at our website. The following policy will help you to understand how we treat and use your personal information. As we continue to improve our site and services we may take advantage of developments in technology. When new technology is put in place, this policy is subject to change. 

**Information Collection and Use**

High Card Marketing, LLC. collects information from our web site in several ways including but not limited to, cookies, sessions, referring websites, website activity, and through data provided by outside services. During registration, High Card Marketing, LLC. asks for some identifying information such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may also be asked for personal information when you report a problem with our site and related services or, if you otherwise contact High Card Marketing, LLC. 

We may require that you provide credit card information, as well as other billing related information when you establish an account with High Card Marketing, LLC. Credit card information is submitted using SSL ( Secure Sockets Layer ), and may be stored offsite on the servers of a PCI Compliant service provider. 

As previously stated High Card Marketing, LLC. collects information using cookies, which are small pieces of data stored by your browser and/or your computer's hard drive. This information allows us to more easily service your account needs and ensure proper tracking of sales in our affiliate referral program. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies unless specifically set not to, use of our website requires cookies. 

High Card Marketing, LLC. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site, however, we do not store any personal information other than what is necessary to provide proper service. We will not sell this information to others, but may provide minimal contact information to selected marketing partners. Information is collected with the sole purpose of providing High Card Marketing, LLC. services. 

When you are on our domain, only High Card Marketing, LLC., its agents and representatives have access to your information. High Card Marketing, LLC. will not disclose any of your personal information except when we have your express permission or under special circumstances, such as when the law requires it. High Card Marketing, LLC. will comply with the requests of all recognized legal entities to aid in the stopping of spam, distribution of illicit sexual content to minors, or any other illegal activity brought to our attention through the proper legal channels. 

High Card Marketing, LLC. may occasionally send you e-mail, contact you via phone, or through postal mail about promotions, service upgrades, and other services that we feel would be of value to your business both with High Card Marketing, LLC., and based on your use of our services. Only High Card Marketing, LLC., or agents or representatives working on behalf of High Card Marketing, LLC., will contact you. 

All High Card Marketing, LLC. affiliate information is collected with for the purpose of properly tracking sales for our affiliate referral system. High Card Marketing, LLC. will not sell, share or rent this information to others. 

This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites unless they are specifically listed in this privacy policy.
